Brothers.
Cai killed our boss.
We must find him no matter what.
I'll tear him into pieces and scatter his bones.
Guys, look carefully.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
You said it was auntie?
No.
Wu Zhen killed your father.
His name is Cai Yun.
No wonder.
You called him Bao.
Uncle.
Please tell me
what happened.
Why did Cai Yun kill my father?
Tell me.
Eagle.
After your father received Huo Lang's letter,
he took me down the mountain.
I didn't expect to see Cai.
Cai Yun threatened your father
to hand over the power of Qinglong Camp.
Your father refused.
So they fought.
With Cai Yun's ability,
you couldn't beat your father.
But...
But what?
But he hit me first.
He hurt my arm.
In order to save me,
to save me.
and forced me to leave first.
Go back to the fortress to get reinforcements.
I don't understand.
He has Black Tiger Mountain.
isn't enough.
A meticulous person
is not that easy
is not easy to fill.
With the status of Qinglong Fortress in the Three Duods,
Black Tiger Mountain is just
a small mountain.
I don’t understand.
You said Cai Yun killed the old man
to steal Qinglong Fortress?
But he did a lot
for Qinglong Camp.
This is the scary part of a person.
Some people are good at disguise themselves
to gain others' trust,
and use everyone's trust
to achieve the ultimate goal step by step.
So...
The name is fake.
I like you
It's fake.
being nice to us
is fake.
How bad is he?
to have so many thoughts.
It's me.
I brought him up the mountain.
I killed my father.
Sister.
It's not your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
You're blaming yourself now.
you'll hurt yourself.
You're right.
I can't fall.
I still have a lot of things to do.
Report!
Master He, Miss Leng.
We went down the mountain
we went down the mountain to find Cai.
but only a pile of blood was found.
but no body was found.
You said there was only a pile of blood, right?
He's dead or dead.
That means he's still alive.
He could be alive.
And someone must have taken him away.
Is Cai Zhen still here?
He's gone to Qinglong Fortress. He's gone to Qinglong Fortress.
Pass my order.
All the swordsmen of the three chiefs capture Cai Yun alive.
Yes, Miss.
I want to know
why he did that.
and kill him with his own hands.
Sister.
Are you okay?
Brother.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I had no choice.
They threatened me with Meixiang and Nini.
I have no choice, brother.
Brother.
A hero, Shangguan Bao,
to eliminate the evil and keep peace.
All the villagers are here.
Mr. Water is here.
Here comes Madam Wu.
My condolences.
Brother.
Take care.
Madam Xi is here.
Madam.
I’ll avenge you.
Don't worry.
I'll still be the same as before.
I will protect Qinglong Fortress and Miss Leopard.
Old Leopard.
Brother
This is the mourning hall, Old Leopard.
Ms. Huo is here.
The dead is the most important. Brother.
Old Leopard!
Brother, the deceased is the most important today.
The victim is the boss today.
Don't mess around.
Old Leopard, get up.
Get up!
Old Leopard.
I've been fighting you for over 20 years.
I'm not done fighting you.
Why are you leaving?
I heard
they lured you down
to lure you down the mountain.
It shows how important I am to you.
Since you're gone,
then just go.
I'll kill those who hurt you
and offer his head to you.
Brother, take care.
Madam.
You saved half a catty from the pursuers.
and swore that
I'll follow you all my life.
You were killed
before I could repay you.
I can't repay you.
I can only swear to God
to catch the murderer
and crush him to ashes.
to worship
in heaven.
Master.
Only you can take charge of the plan in the fortress.
You will take us to revenge, right?
Master.
Yes.
Okay.
I'll ask you for the punishment.
When I find the murderer,
I’ll kill him myself
and avenge Madam.
I’ll help you.
Brother.
Goodbye.
Everyone.
The Fortress of the Three Families
led by Qinglong Fortress,
and the leader of Qinglong Fortress.
Now she’s dead.
The Fortress of the Forty-Eight has no leader.
It’s time to choose someone
to replace him.
and bring us back together.
That's right.
We have to choose someone
and capable
to take over the position of Patriarch.
You’re the leaders of the Fortress.
Do you have any idea?
I’ll follow the lead of Qinglong Fortress.
I dare not
the position of Patriarch.
I'm used to staying in QinFo Ye's valley.
There are too many rules in Qinglong Camp.
I can’t stand it.
You can choose whoever you want.
Master Shui.
What you said
is the same as what I thought.
We're not someone who can worry.
Well, no matter who you recommend,
as long as you believe me,
No objection.
Fine.
I'll recommend Eagle
Eagle is my brother's daughter.
He's always nice to his brothers.
and very capable.
I think she's suitable to take over this fortress.
Yes.
Eagle is the daughter of the Patriarch.
That's right.
But in terms of seniority and seniority,
Mr. He should be the most respectable.
Mr. He
was Leader’s right-hand man.
He takes care of
in the village.
In terms of ability, he's more suitable to be the head.
Liu.
You're wrong.
When Master He came,
when Mr. He came.
Now his daughter will take over his business.
to take over his business.
The leader of swordsmen has a great responsibility.
This concerns the lives of thousands of brothers.
They are always capable.
There's no such thing as inheriting his father's career.
Besides, we're facing a great enemy.
Eagle is just a girl.
No matter how smart she is,
but lack experience.
How can I lead everyone
to fight against those fierce enemies?
Fine.
Since we don't play together,
let us vote fairly.
Raise your hand if you recommend her.
Raise your hand.
Raise your hand if you support Mr. He!
Support Mr. He! Support him!
It’s over.
Thank you
and bros.
I know you made this choice
because of my father.
I will also contribute
for Qinglong Fortress.
But I know my place.
If it were in the past, I would have done nothing wrong.
But now, judging from the situation,
and my ability.
I can't do it.
If I really take the lead,
I'll only give the enemy a chance to get in.
Please think twice.
Eagle, we're willing to
We are willing to do it.
We will support you together.
and sit on this chair.
But Qinglong Fortress has no leader now.
If anything goes wrong,
your family business
will disappear.
Uncle Liu, you are right.
Qinglong Fortress
needs a respectable elder.
My choice
is Mr. He. Mr. He.
Eagle, no.
No!
I’m just like you.
like you.
I will never do
betray you.
Qinglong Fortress has only one surname.
That is Shangguan.
I'm willing to help you
to handle the business of the fortress.
Uncle.
you and my father
with my father.
You’ve been in charge of
all these years.
We all know that.
right?
Yes.
Please take the position of Patriarch for now.
I’m flattered.
I'm willing to be your pawn.
Please focus on the future of Qinglong Camp.
Don't refuse.
Eagle.
I'll take care of Qinglong Fortress for you.
I know everyone is doing this for Qinglong Fortress.
but I can't ruin this family business.
I beg you
to help Master He
and revive Qinglong Camp.
Miss, we’ll listen to you.
Mr. He. Mr. He.
Just let me know if you need anything.
We’ll do our best.
Leader He.
You’re awake.
I...
What's wrong with me?
We're no longer friends.
Eagle.
Eagle wants to kill me.
I remember now.
I...
Where am I?
This is a temporary accommodation assigned by the organization.
Stay here and recuperate.
When you recover,
the organization will arrange for you to leave Shanzhou.
Leave Shanzhou?
Why?
The news of you killing Shangguan Bao has spread.
Shangguan Eagle must kill you.
Now all the swordsmen are looking for you.
What are you doing?
I'm going to find Eagle.
and explain everything to her.
Calm down. Sit down.
You can't explain it to her now.
There will be a chance.
I'm worried that Eagle will be used.
Zheng Xiong Tian Yuan has been eyeing
Qinglong Camp.
No.
Just like her father,
will never be bribed by others.
Wen Pei is right.
Eagle won’t be easily used.
But who is the murderer who killed Madam?
I need to get well soon.
I still have a lot of things to do.
I think
the murderer who killed Madam
must have something to do with the Japanese.
If Zheng Xiong Tahara is the mastermind,
he must have an accomplice.
Shangguan Bao has been in the three realms for decades.
to easily lure him down the mountain
and kill him.
and framed me.
This must be a well-designed conspiracy.
And this helper
must be trusted by Shangguan Bao.
His identity
is beyond our imagination.
According to you,
if Qinglong Fortress falls into his hands,
it will be controlled by the Japanese.
That's too dangerous.
No, I have to
to the superiors
and then make plans.
Time is precious. I'm counting on you.
Don't worry.
Just take care of yourself.
Leave the rest to me.
Here.
Wen Pei.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Sister.
There's something I don't understand.
Go ahead.
I don't understand
why she chose such a faraway place
to kill him?
He is familiar with Qinglong Fortress.
There are many opportunities to take action.
You don't have to fool me out.
You mean
someone framed Cai?
No, no.
That's not what I meant.
I...
I just...
Sister.
Uncle, I want to ask you something.
Go ahead, Eagle.
Who sent the letter
who sent the letter that disguised as Huo Lang?
The letter was on the case in the lobby.
I found it and gave it to your father.
Eagle.
Does it matter who sent the letter?
Why did you suddenly ask about this today?
I just think the person who sent the letter
has something to do with my father's death.
There are many people in the hall every day,
but I was the only one
that day.
Only you.
After that, I asked all the guards on guard
and I've never seen anyone sending letters.
His whereabouts are so secretive.
I think he must be familiar with
He knows the terrain of the fortress very well.
Eagle.
At this point,
I have to remind you
I have to remind you.
Go ahead.
Based on your relationship with Pahra Chae,
he was your fiancé.
It's inevitable that he still has feelings for you.
But now that he killed your father,
he has become the enemy of the swordsman.
I hope you can tell right from wrong.
[Don't be troubled by love.]
Avenge your father as soon as possible
and calm the anger of our brothers.
and comfort
your father's soul in heaven.
You're right.
I'll keep that in mind.
From now on, all you care about is revenge.
I have no other thoughts.
I will carry on your will
and restore Qinglong Stronghold.
Rest in peace.
Eagle.
You came here.
I didn’t kill Leader.
It’s all Japanese’s conspiracy.
Conspiracy?
I think it's your conspiracy.
You did everything you could
to get the power of Qinglong Camp.
You are as hateful as the Japanese.
Eagle, listen to me.
The Japanese framed me.
to make Qinglong Fortress
turn against each other.
Don’t fall into their trap.
In the end, you’ll regret your death.
Shut up!
Eagle, let me explain.
There seems to be noise in the courtyard.
Let's go and have a look.
Let's go.
Let's take a look.
Eagle, calm down.
Let me explain.
What's there to explain?
Eagle.
I know you're sad now.
but can you hear me out?
Come on, see what's going on.
Hurry.
I...
We have a deep misunderstanding.
I'll find another chance
to explain to you.
Chae Bo-ra!
Guys, catch him!
Stop!
Hurry! Don't let him escape!
Hurry!
Don't let him get away! Catch him!
Stop!
Where are you going?
Go after him!
Stop!
Over there!
Stop! Stop!
Follow me.
What's going on? Go after him!
Okay, let's go.
Mr. Liu.
How dare you come back?
Listen to the sound of killing outside.
Those swordsmen want to kill you.
For Qinglong Camp,
I have to come back.
I guess I was right.
You are not the murderer.
Don’t you think I killed Madam?
If you killed her,
how dare you come back?
Trust me.
It’s Madam who trusts you.
And I believe you.
It seems
I’m not alone
in Qinglong Camp.
What are you going to do next?
You mean
there will be a huge change in Qinglong Camp.
If we can’t find the Japanese,
who helped the Japanese,
Qinglong Camp will be doomed.
I'll investigate the murderer.
In my identity,
I'm more suitable to walk in Qinglong Fortress than you.
I’m worried
that the swordsmen on the boat
because of hatred.
It's confusing
in a mess.
You're right.
I have to hurry back
and discuss with the organization.
Let's go. I'll take you out.
Many people ran away
many people ran away. Stop!
I heard about it too.
Let's go.
I don't know what to do with our village.
Life is hard.
Let's go.
Stop!
Sir.
Who are you looking for?
We are looking for the murderer.
The murderer who killed our boss.
Don’t talk nonsense.
Isn’t your boss Shangguan Bao?
Who can kill Shangguan Bao?
He is so skilled.
Stop talking nonsense. Let's go.
Stop!
Go over there.
Thank you.
Li.
Miss Leng.
Where are we going?
Let’s go down the mountain for revenge.
Mr. He said this morning
Madam was killed by Cai
by Cai Ninzi and the National Party.
So we went down the mountain to avenge Madam.
You go down the mountain to seek revenge from the National Party.
Yes, find Jang Gong-yeon to pay his blood debt.
Why didn't anyone
such a big thing?
We thought the head told you.
Comrade Cai.
You are injured.
Why did you act on your own?
I have to find Shangguan Eagle
and tell her the truth.
The murderer must still be on the move.
As time goes by,
the more she will be deceived.
Tell her and let her understand.
She and Qinglong Fortress
will not fall into the hands of Zheng Xiong Tachihara.
But she can't trust you now.
She thinks you killed her father.
and lost her mind.
You can't be as impulsive as her.
What can I do?
Watching her and the swordsman
slowly being manipulated
by the murderer?
They are 100,000 swordsmen.
Now they are like a double-edged sword.
It’s good for anti-Japanese.
If it falls into the enemy's hands,
we can't imagine
what will happen.
Not to mention you're injured,
even if you walk to three levels,
your life will be in danger.
Our career cannot avoid sacrifices.
But it's not for nothing.
No, I tried so hard
Why can't you understand?
My comrade Cui WenPei.
Time waits for no one.
I'll find Shangguan Eagle.
Actor table.
Zhang Wen.
and actors.
Yue, Wang, Yang Ziyi, Tian Chenzhe, Deng Kai. Mei Liangdong.
Li, Yu Hongda, Tian Guofeng, Gong, Fan. Cheng Kaiyan.
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengseng, Yang Haoyu, Callow.
Yang Ziyi, Tian Chenzhe, Deng Kai, Mei Liangdong
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao Sun Hao.
Wang Jinjun Liu Jiawen.
Ji, Chao, Zhao Zhigang, Kung, Ji Youyi. Peng Zhenfu.
Xu Fu and Wu Jianyu Zhang Guangyan Sun Yuanwen Chang Qing.
Wu Jinxing, Feng Yonghao, Wei Long, Deng Bao Quan.
Qin HaoSen, Liu Mingjun, Zhang Lianglin.
The legendary army, Liu Hongguo, Yang Chenglin, Liu Yinlong.
Li Zhendong, Chi, Rui, Zhang Ke'er, Yang Junjie. Cui Yuseok.
Zhao Jianhao, Li Xiaoyan, Dong Qisun.
Staff list.
Director team.
The production team.
Feng Xiaogang.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
Tian Shuizhou.
The clothing team.
Shi Jangyeong.
The dressing team.
Art team.
Props team.
Ye Qing.
Set team.
Set team leader, Yang Longfei.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
Sun Hai.
The recording team.
Wang Wenbo.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Rong Xijun.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Jiang Jiping.
Wang Bao Cheung, Su Gao Feng, Liu Deyu, Zhai Yongming. Zou Youwei.
Zhang Chenggui, Su Mingxin, Liu Hongxing, Di Yuping Xu Guanglle.
Xu Ian, Zhang Shou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Shou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Ge Wenlong, Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang Zhang Jian Ping.
Cut.
and group DIT.
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
Ma Jun Nan.
Liu Liu.
A dubber.
Music production.
Theme song, Hero.
composing songs.
Rex.
Singer: Wei Ningfeng Qin Yidan
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District.
The Civil Affairs of Xizhang Village, Seozhou District.
The temple in Shanzhou District.
[Seobu Village Committee of Lingbao City]
Original store is in a fork.
Zhou family in the city.
[Legal Consultant]
The legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
The People's Government
There are three branches in total.
There are three marketing departments in total.
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
Zhongtong Municipal County Commission.
Henan Henan Yunyang Liquor Co., Ltd.
The People's Government of Laji County.
Henan Henan Boutique Co., Ltd.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
[Sanmen Lanhu City Wetland Park]
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
[Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association]
TV station.
Henan Provincial Film Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Gansu Lanyi Culture Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film Production Co., Ltd.
Henan Movie Development Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quan Zhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Zhang Bing will be rewarded first.